[
Music]
Hello friends, welcome to the Option Gyan channel.
Friends,
today I am talking about a stock in the position stop category.
Its name is APL Limited. Friends, if you are
connected to the My Stocks channel
and if you fold the stock that I am giving on my channel
properly, then
you must have made a
good profit. Your
portfolio must have come in the green.
Although some stocks are
trading below the rate at which I gave them, but
if you have given the base rate of Everest to them also, then I have given the
base rate of Everest in my video
and if you have declared them illegal, then they would have
either lost their cost
or the matter would have returned to you.
But overall, your profile would have
come in IGNOU
that the person who has taken the stock of PM Limited,
its fundamentals are very strong. Its
52-week high
is around 1150 and 52-week low is 10. So,
you find it right
around its 52-week low, so you
should definitely share it here
because the fundamentals of the company are also very strong.  It
is strong, I will discuss that too with you,
but once you read and discuss it,
where to click, where to
wish and edit here, then
friends, you have to put
only 30% of your slipper around the current i.e. 724
and the remaining 30% you will
put around 725
and the remaining 40% of yours, friends,
you have to put it around 1622, if the
stock remains below 1622 for three-four days,
then you will exit your position,
hello friends, you will have to
give time in the market, if you
give three-four years time in the market, then you will be
enough, your knowledge will become very good,
your profit will be less once,
but your knowledge will become very good
and your profit will also gradually increase,
your portfolio will be
seen increasing and you people will
also start getting tax fiction,
your confidence will increase a lot, so that is why
I always tell you people  I will give a stop loss
that if it goes below that then
you guys have to unite so that to
save your wicket, we
discuss it fundamentally in the market
that Dubai Jaroda's account, my points of this mask
stock, click on it, then it
comes to mind, click on fundamentals
and click on details here,
which is given on the top side, then it
takes you to the ticket
that you have created a react investment
checklist, keep Pandey in this circle, out of this
you will see four points in
green, if we
talk about the company's team furniture trend, then
you people must be seeing it very positive
that from 2018 to 2021 there is opposition from investment
and their profit is also increasing,
if we talk about the pension statement, then
that too is
looking positive, the company's which
goes to the soldiers friends due to opposition from the industry, the company has also increased its market
and the company's Jio net income is
more than the 90% of the industry,
I think the company overall is quite good, you people  You
can convert this into your portfolio so
friends I hope you
liked this video and it will be very beneficial for you
with this friends
I end my video thank you
so friends if you like this video
please don't forget to like share and subscribe
thank you for watching my video
[music]